http://www.tutor.com/privacy#ccpa

Military Families
The official provider of online tutoring and homework help to the Department of Defense.
Check Eligibility
Higher Education
Improve persistence and course completion with 24/7 student support online.
How it Works
Public Libraries
Engage your community with learning and career services for patrons of all ages.
Learn More
Corporate Partners
Support your workforce and their families with a unique employee benefit.
Get Started
Tutor.com is now part of The Princeton Review!
Sign In
19,851,266 Sessions and Counting!
Effective Date: June 30, 2020
Tutor.com, Inc. and its subsidiaries, including TPR Education, LLC d/b/a The Princeton Review (collectively, “we,” “us,” or “our”) take your privacy seriously and understand the importance of protecting your personal information. Therefore, this Privacy Policy provides information about our privacy practices.
By visiting the websites located at www.princetonreview.com
and at www.tutor.com
and other websites and mobile applications which link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, “Sites”) or using the products or services offered through this Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into the Terms of Use for this Site.
For Parents of Children under the Age of 13
For any user under the age of 13, whose personal information we collect, we must have permission from such user’s parent or legal guardian before we collect or use any personal information of such user on the Site. You are welcome to contact us at 800-2REVIEW or prep@review.com
to review any personal information we have collected about your child. You may request that we delete this information or specify that we collect no more of your child’s information. We will need to verify the identity of anyone requesting information about a child under the age of 13 to ensure that the person is in fact the child’s parent or legal guardian.
Information We Collect
We collect information through the sources described below.
Information You Provide to Us.
We collect personal information and non-personal information from you (such as your or your parents’ or guardians’ name, address, email address, phone number, credit card number, school name, grade level, year of graduation, date of birth, GPA, test scores, academic interests, transcripts, photos, employer name and job title, library card number, race, and military or veteran status) when you:
register or create an account on our Site;
call us;
purchase our products or services;
provide us or upload to our Site messages, documents, and other files and content in the course of your use of our products or services;
enter sweepstakes or other promotions;
respond to surveys or questionnaires or submit testimonials;
provide us information at events we host, sponsor, or participate in;
provide us information on our Site or submit online forms so that we can contact you about products or services you may be interested in or answer questions you have; or
when you provide us information by other means.
Information from Third Parties.
We may collect personal and non-personal information about you (such as your name, email address, student ID number, grade level, and courses you are taking) from third parties with whom we have a business relationship (such as our organizational customers, resellers, licensees, and franchisees).
We may receive information about you from our users who refer you to us and from college and universities for the purpose of conducting surveys.
We may obtain personal and non-personal information from publicly and commercially available sources, including organizers of events you may attend.
Information Collected Automatically.
We collect information (such as your IP address, your browser type, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us, the referring website address, and operating system) from your browser when you visit our Site.
We, our service providers and other vendors, and our affiliates and third parties which may display advertisement on our Site may use tracking technologies such as cookies and pixel tags to collect information about your online interactions with our Site and our emails.
We collect information when you purchase our products and services and use our products and services (such as recording online sessions, producing transcripts of online tutoring sessions, and tracking the drills and practice tests that you take online).
We automatically record calls to our call center.
How We Use Information
We may use your personal information to:
provide you with and personalize our products and services;
create and manage your account, process your orders, and provide you customer service;
maintain our internal records and otherwise manage our business;
send you newsletters and advertisements and otherwise correspond with you about products, services, events, and other organizations that we think may interest you;
ask for your reviews and testimonials and send you surveys and questionnaires;
improve our products, services, and Site;
administer sweepstakes and other promotions;
develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our Site and other sites, provide our advertisements to you when you visit other sites, and analyze the effectiveness of our advertisements;
perform research and analysis about your use of or interest in our products and services, the products or services offered by others, and our Site, and develop new products and services;
detect, prevent, or investigate illegal activity or misuse of our products or services and enforce our legal rights; and
perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.
We may use non-personal information for any lawful purpose.
Third Parties to whom We Disclose Information
We share your information with third parties as described below. We do not disclose your personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes except as described under “Schools You are Interested in” and “Licensees and Franchisees” below.
Organizations and Persons who Arrange for Your Participation in Our Programs
We work with schools, school districts, colleges and universities, local, state, and federal government agencies, businesses, and other organizations to provide programs such as tutoring, test preparation, and college admission counseling. Your organization may arrange for your participation in these programs and negotiate a special price or trial offer, or purchase (or subsidize) products or services on your behalf. We may share your personal and non-personal information that we collect through your participation in these programs (such as test scores, transcripts or recordings of online tutoring and online class sessions, comments you leave in post-session surveys, and details regarding your usage of our programs) with the organization arranging for your access to these programs or with your parents or guardians. In addition, your school may require us to share such information with others legally entitled to access your academic records, such as your state department of education. If you use a promotion code at our Site to create an account or add products or services, we may let the source of that promotion code know that you used that code.
Service Providers and Other Vendors
We may share your personal information with our service providers and other vendors, such as those who help deliver our products and services, process transactions (such as charging your credit card when you make purchases), market our products and services, obtain reviews and testimonials, and otherwise help us operate our business.
Schools You are Interested in
You may direct the disclosure of your personal information to the schools on our Site for their direct marketing purposes by selecting “Request School Info” or “Request Info” next to the schools on our Site or selecting “Select All Schools” from the search results of schools that match your interests. If you do not want to share your personal information with the schools, do not select the options listed above.
Licensees and Franchisees
If you are located outside the United States and Canada, we may share your personal information with our licensees and franchisees in your location who may market their products and services to you. If you uncheck “I’d like to receive promotional offers, informative content, product updates and more” under your account settings for The Princeton Review, then we will stop such sharing, but licensees and franchisees who previously received your personal information may continue to market their products and services to you.
Affiliates
We may share your personal information with our affiliates.
Legally Compelled Disclosures and Safety
We may disclose personal information when compelled to do so by government authorities or otherwise as required or permitted by law, such as to respond to court orders and subpoenas. We may also disclose personal information to protect the safety of others and when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interfering with our rights or property or the rights or property of others.
Business Transfer
If we or all or a portion of our business is acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, personal information may be included in the transferred assets.
Authorized Disclosure
We may share your personal information with third parties when you authorize the disclosure.
Non-Personal Information
We may share non-personal Information with any third party for any lawful purpose.
Your Access to Information
If you have an account with us, you may review and correct the information that is accessible to you under the settings for your account on our Site or by calling 800-2REVIEW.
Opting Out of Promotional Correspondence
You may elect not to receive promotional correspondence from us. If you have an account with us, you may make this request under the settings for your account by indicating which correspondence you would like to receive. You can also send an e-mail to  prep@review.com . In this e-mail, please say whether: (i) you would like to opt out of receiving all e-mail promotional correspondence from us in general or (ii) if you would only like to opt out of certain of our e-newsletters or correspondence and if so which ones or (iii) you would like to opt out of receiving SMS or text messages. You may also opt out of our promotional e-mails by clicking on an opt-out link within the e-mail you receive.
Please understand that if you opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us.
Using Caution when Sharing Information with Others
When you contribute to a public area or feature of our Site, such as a chat room, bulletin board, list serve, blog, or wiki, the information that you submit will be made available to the general public. Therefore, we recommend that you do not submit any sensitive information to such areas of our Site, including your full name, home address, phone number, financial information or any other information that would enable other users to locate you or contact you.
Other Sites
When you are on our Site, you may be able to visit or link to other sites not operated by us. We do not control such sites and are not responsible for the information practices of these sites. This Privacy Policy does not address the information practices of those other websites, and we encourage you to read the posted privacy policies of such sites.
Nevada Privacy Rights
We do not sell the personal information of Nevada consumers without their authorization, but Nevada consumers may submit an email to prep@review.com
to request that we do not sell their personal information in the future.
California Consumer Privacy Act Rights
The information in this California Consumer Privacy Act Rights section applies only to California consumers. Any terms defined in the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) have the same meaning when used in this California Consumer Privacy Act Rights section.
Personal Information We Collect
We may collect, and in the past 12 months have collected, the following categories of personal information:
Identifiers (such as name, address, email, cookies, IP address, date of birth, student ID number, and library card number)
Categories of personal information listed in the California Customer Records statute (such as phone number, credit card number, and education)
Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law (such as military or veteran status and race)
Commercial information (such as purchase history)
Internet or other electronic network activity information (such as interaction with our Sites)
Non-public education information (per the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C. Section 1232g, 34 C.F.R. Part 99)) (such as test scores, GPA, course enrollments, and transcripts)
Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information (such as recorded voice, recorded video, and photos)
Professional or employment-related information (such as employer information and job title)
Inferences drawn from other categories of personal information to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, or aptitudes (such as likelihood of making a purchase based on internet or other electronic network activity)
Sources from which Personal Information is Collected
We collect personal information from the categories of sources listed below, as described in more detail in the “Information We Collect” section above:
Consumers
Third parties with whom we have a business relationship (such as our organizational customers, resellers, licensees, and franchisees)
Other users who refer you to us
College and universities who provide information for the purpose of conducting surveys
Publicly and commercially available sources, including organizers of events you may attend
Browsers and tracking technologies
Our service providers and other vendors
Purposes for which Personal Information Will Be Used
We may use personal information for the following purposes:
provide you with and personalize our products and services;
create and manage your account, process your orders, and provide you customer service;
maintain our internal records and otherwise manage our business;
send you newsletters and advertisements and otherwise correspond with you about products, services, events, and other organizations that we think may interest you;
ask for your reviews and testimonials and send you surveys and questionnaires;
improve our products, services, and Site;
administer sweepstakes and other promotions;
develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our Site and other sites, provide our advertisements to you when you visit other sites, and analyze the effectiveness of our advertisements;
perform research and analysis about your use of or interest in our products and services, the products or services offered by others, and our Site, and develop new products and services;
detect, prevent, or investigate illegal activity or misuse of our products or services and enforce our legal rights; and
perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.
Personal Information Sold or Disclosed for a Business Purpose
We do not sell personal information of California consumers, have not sold personal information of California consumers in the preceding 12 months, and do not have actual knowledge that we sell the personal information of minors under 16 years of age.
We may disclose personal information to a third party for a business purpose. In the preceding 12 months, we have disclosed the categories of personal information listed below to organizations and persons who arranged for consumers' participation in our products and services and our service providers and other vendors:
Identifiers
Categories of personal information listed in the California Customer Records statute
Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law
Commercial information
Internet or other electronic network activity information
Non-public education information
Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information
Professional or employment-related information
Inferences drawn from other categories of personal information
Your Right to Know
You have the right to request that we disclose information to you about our collection, use, disclosure, and sale of your personal information in the 12-month period preceding your request. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, then subject to exceptions provided under the CCPA and based on your request, we will disclose to you:
The categories of personal information we collected about you.
The categories of sources from which we collected your personal information.
The business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling your personal information.
The categories of third parties with whom we shared your personal information.
The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you.
If we sold your personal information, the categories of personal information that was sold to each category of recipient.
If we disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, the categories of personal information that was disclosed to each category of recipient.
Your Right to Deletion
You have the right to request that we delete your personal information that we have collected, subject to exceptions provided under the CCPA. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, then unless an exception applies, we will delete your personal information from our records and direct our service providers and other vendors to delete your personal information from their records.
Your Right to Non-Discrimination
You have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment by us for the exercise of the privacy rights conferred by the CCPA.
Submitting Requests
To exercise your right to know or right to deletion described above, please submit a verifiable consumer request to us by:
Calling us at 888-223-7737; or
Completing a request form located at www.princetonreview.com/ccpa
and www.tutor.com/ccpa
mailing it to the address listed on the form.
You may only make a verifiable consumer request to know twice within a 12-month period.
You may authorize another person to act as your agent to submit requests on your behalf. Unless you provide the agent with power of attorney under the California Probate Code, you will need to provide the agent a written and signed authorization. You may also submit requests on behalf of your minor child.
Verification
We will verify your identity before fulfilling your request. If you have an account with us, we will ask you to enter your username and password through a link we provide to verify your identity. If you do not have an account with us, we will ask you to provide us data points that we have about you to verify your identity.
If you authorize another person to act as your agent to submit requests on your behalf, then unless you provide the agent with power of attorney under the California Probate Code, we will ask the agent to provide us the written and signed authorization that you provided to the agent, we will confirm with you that you did provide the authorization, and we will verify your identity. If you submit a request on behalf of a minor child, we will ask you to provide us information about your child that allows us to determine that you are the parent or guardian of the child. If the child is under the age of 13, we will ask you to sign a form declaring under penalty of perjury that you are the parent or guardian of the child.
Our Response to Your Request
We endeavor to respond to a verifiable consumer request within 45 days of its receipt.  If we require more time (up to 45 additional days), we will inform you of the reason in writing.  We will deliver our written response by mail or electronically.  If we are unable to comply with a request, our response will explain why.
We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable consumer request unless it is excessive or manifestly unfounded. If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request.
Accessibility of this Privacy Policy
Commercially available screen reader programs should be able to read this Privacy Policy. As a web page, this Privacy Policy may be printed as a document.
Users Outside of the United States
By providing personal information to this Site, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories, in accordance with applicable law. We are a United States company and we do not operate in or market to individuals in the European Economic Area (“EEA”). Any processing of personal data of individuals in the EEA by us is incidental. We do, however, recognize the rights of individuals in the EEA and, therefore, request that any individuals located in the EEA who have questions about or requests related to the personal data we collect to contact us at prep@review.com .
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We will update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “Effective Date” at the top of this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check our Site from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, you may contact us by email or mail at the following address:
The Princeton Review and Tutor.com
110 E. 42nd Street, 7th Floor
New York, NY 10017
Attention: Legal Department
privacy@review.com
Privacy
Learn more
FAQ
For more information call us at:
800-411-1970
© 2020 Tutor.com / The Princeton Review - Not Affiliated with Princeton University.
Privacy Policy  |
CCPA Privacy Notice |
Terms of Use
